<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<subcorpus num_sub="7" year="2016.0" month="10.0" subreddit="bostonceltics" handle="bostonceltics_2016.0-10.0"><submission author_name="celticsbig4" subreddit_name="bostonceltics" created_utc="1475346550.0" edited="False" has_media="False" gilded="0" score="67" title="A look at Smart's new shooting form" id="55eh6b" domain="self.bostonceltics" url="https://www.reddit.com/r/bostonceltics/comments/55eh6b/a_look_at_smarts_new_shooting_form/" permalink="/r/bostonceltics/comments/55eh6b/a_look_at_smarts_new_shooting_form/?ref=search_posts" locked="False" over_18="False" stickied="False" is_self="True" num_reports="" num_com_found="22" num_com_listed="22" handle="bostonceltics_2016.0-10.0">https://youtu.be/LJXLqkp3-pw

There's still a dip but it's quick, almost unnoticeable compared to the huge dip in his shot last year. Feet are set more consistently as well, which was probably the biggest problem with his shot even in college. It looks like he's getting set quicker and and having a consistent overall motion, but it's only training camp so we'll see what happens once real games start.<comments><comment created_utc="1475347199.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89u2f2" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">He had at least two really clean catch-and-shoot threes go in during the scrimmage. He didn't have to chuck a bunch of wild ones to get in a groove, either. </comment><comment created_utc="1475349574.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89vl0r" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">Not only does this new form save time on the shot but I'm sure it saves him some energy too. That old form had way too much built into it. </comment><comment created_utc="1475366947.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a6kik" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">Its because his hair is shorter and no longer in the way (please get this reference...)</comment><comment created_utc="1475350251.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89w0qw" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">Here's Jared's video for even better quality: https://twitter.com/JaredWeissNBA/status/782247192602021888</comment><comment created_utc="1475352756.0" edited="1475353127.0" gilded="0" id="d89xmgr" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">Looks a lot smoother and simpler. In previous seasons, there appeared to be too much motion before going into the shot.</comment><comment created_utc="1475380201.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8ae8c4" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">It appears to go in. I like it.</comment><comment created_utc="1475351953.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89x3qs" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">WTF? - Am I watching a video of Devin Booker??? That's crazy. Great find OP. With that video and his performance yesterday - he could be a legit 3 and D guy. And what's awesome is he also looked really good coming screens at the 2. I always thought of him as a PG but now I am not sure? </comment><comment created_utc="1475348981.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89v7jj" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">It looks like he's working on exactly what he needs to be working on. Good for him; I can't wait to see it in action</comment><comment created_utc="1475385289.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8agu0m" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">I will believe it when I see it.  Not to be a negative nancy, Smarts one of my binkys, but we hear these kinds of things all the time.  If he can get to 37%+ from three he's going to be a hell of a player.  </comment><comment created_utc="1475368797.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a7nq2" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">He doesn't seem to have much elevation on this shot at all... Which is fine if he is being encouraged to shoot only open jumpers... but inevitably; if you handle the ball you will need to shoot contested shots, which will mean changing your shot significantly and resulting in his contested shots % going down (if that is even possible). </comment><comment created_utc="1475373353.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aabk7" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">holy shit that is so much smoother than before. The horrible dip is gone and mechanics are much more efficient. HYPE HYPE HYPE HYPE</comment><comment created_utc="1475389099.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aiegw" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">He doesn't hurl the ball at the hoop anymore. It's more consistent and it's quicker. I love it</comment><comment created_utc="1475506567.0" edited="1475513563.0" gilded="0" id="d8c5uvp" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">As we have been saying for two years. If he can improve his offense to just bad instead of historically bad, he will be MUCH more valuable than he already was. If his offense gets to above average he will be a star. </comment><comment created_utc="1475354080.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89yhso" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89vl0r" controversiality="0">The old form looked like he was in pain while shooting it. It seemed so laborious and difficult. This one looks nice and smooth. I hope it results in better percentages for him, although his biggest issue is still shot selection. </comment><comment created_utc="1475470095.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8brly8" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a6kik" controversiality="0">:) </comment><comment created_utc="1475363341.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a4ee2" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89w0qw" controversiality="0">Dip is so much nicer now. Kinda looks like pierces shot to me.</comment><comment created_utc="1475380707.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aei8j" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89xmgr" controversiality="0">Yea, he would bring the ball almost all the way to the top back part of his head.  It was ridiculous.  He like, catapulted it.  This looks a lot different and a lot better.  The less movement in the shooting form, the easier it is to replicate.  </comment><comment created_utc="1475434044.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8b2xzo" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89xmgr" controversiality="0">His shot had 2 unnecessary chamber motions. One was the dip at his knees and the other was at his head. </comment><comment created_utc="1475356717.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a08kz" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89x3qs" controversiality="0">3 and D? cmon man he can be so much more.</comment><comment created_utc="1475388275.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8ai3fn" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a7nq2" controversiality="0">Don't know why you're being downvoted since it's a valid point. A shooting style with a low hop helps with consistency and maintain accuracy when you're tired, but it can be blocked easier. This is why Curry's main go-to moves are screens, and mastered dribbling/footwork to create separation during 1v1. A lot of guards shoot with a high hop and two-stroke motion ala Kobe/Jordan style because they aren't usually the tallest and need to make contested shots in traffic. You can have more than one shooting form, but not everyone can perfect all of them or use the right one by instinct every time. Pierce have multiple shooting forms but it took him years to develop and he adapted his game as he aged. </comment><comment created_utc="1475430687.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8b0bmf" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a4ee2" controversiality="0">I see it a little bit too man, good catch. </comment><comment created_utc="1475360166.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a2ev3" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a08kz" controversiality="0">You got me man. What was I thinking? 😉</comment></comments></submission>
<submission author_name="RonFucking_Swanson" subreddit_name="bostonceltics" created_utc="1475325865.0" edited="False" has_media="False" gilded="0" score="62" title="[Himmelsbach] The enduring bond between Kevin Garnett &amp; Celtics strength coach Bryan Doo" id="55d1oi" domain="bostonglobe.com" url="http://www.bostonglobe.com/sports/celtics/2016/09/30/celtics-assistant-recalls-his-special-bond-with-kevin-garnett/tCiYmf0qwyBMX9b4oR54ZO/story.html" permalink="/r/bostonceltics/comments/55d1oi/himmelsbach_the_enduring_bond_between_kevin/?ref=search_posts" locked="False" over_18="False" stickied="False" is_self="False" num_reports="" num_com_found="10" num_com_listed="10" handle="bostonceltics_2016.0-10.0"><comments><comment created_utc="1475328319.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89iz5y" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55d1oi" controversiality="0">I could read Doo tales all day</comment><comment created_utc="1475351311.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89wooc" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55d1oi" controversiality="0">This picture will always be Bryan Doo to me  http://i.imgur.com/6EtLMIF.jpg </comment><comment created_utc="1475332709.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89l2il" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55d1oi" controversiality="0">Fucking love Doo</comment><comment created_utc="1475333964.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89lqyz" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55d1oi" controversiality="0">I wonder who Bryan's close to on the team these days? I only know him and Terry interacting semi-frequently on Instagram.</comment><comment created_utc="1475382163.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8afaqa" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55d1oi" controversiality="0">Can anyone possibly paste the article here? It wont let me view without paying .99 cents. I refuse to do it out of principal. </comment><comment created_utc="1475346375.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89tjme" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55d1oi" controversiality="0">Great stuff.</comment><comment created_utc="1475439970.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8b7q9g" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89wooc" controversiality="0">Oh man I remember when this was posted around lmao</comment><comment created_utc="1475418519.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8as1is" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89lqyz" controversiality="0">Bryan is my roommates uncle, I've heard that he's really close with IT</comment><comment created_utc="1475403178.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8amkjv" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8afaqa" controversiality="0">Celtics strength coach Bryan Doo almost always dresses modestly. At practices, he wears shorts and a Celtics T-shirt. At games, he wears a Celtics polo and tan slacks. And that is about as fancy as he likes to be.

When the team traveled to the White House after winning the 2008 NBA title, Doo packed his only suit, which he had owned since graduating from high school in 1991.

Celtics forward Kevin Garnett instantly noticed the worn-down suit. He asked Doo how old it was.

“You just met the President of the United States in that?” Garnett said. “We can’t have you wearing that anymore.”

After the Celtics returned home, Garnett arranged for Doo to have a suit custom made. Then he realized that other staff members could use upgrades, too. So a representative from Ralph Lauren measured almost 20 of them for new suits, and Garnett paid for them.

“That,” Doo said, “was just the kind of guy that KG was.”

Avery Bradley is the only current Celtic who played with Garnett, so when the 40-year-old star retired last week after 21 pro seasons (six in Boston), it did not resonate strongly with this group.

But for Doo, now in his 14th season in Boston, Garnett’s departure stirs raw emotions. The 6-foot-11-inch player and the 5-foot-6-inch strength coach shared an uncommon bond.

Doo saw the relentless competitor we all saw. But he also saw Garnett’s soft side, his good deeds, his heart. He saw that when you wear your old high school suit to the White House, Kevin Garnett will make everything right.

“I’ve worked in a lot of sports,” Doo said, “and I’ve watched him be the best teammate of any athlete I’ve ever seen.”


When Garnett was traded from the Timberwolves to the Celtics in 2007, his connection with Doo was not instant. He was set in his ways, his rhythms, and he was leery of having his routine disturbed by an outsider.

So Doo would prod subtly, suggesting small adjustments to Garnett’s training approach.

“Look,” Garnett would respond. “I was the league MVP before I met you.”

So Doo focused on minor issues. He told Garnett that if he did not change, he would be susceptible to an injury. Then in January 2008, Garnett was sidelined by an abdominal strain. He was then ready to listen.

“I think he realized that I care about him as a person,” Doo said. “I think that was tough for him to accept, but he realized I was there for him.”

Garnett changed the team’s culture almost instantly. When Garnett was injured and not in the locker room, Doo said, other players tended to act out. When Garnett was there, they did not. Doo recalled a practice when coach Doc Rivers was trying to get the younger big men to understand their roles.

“KG just goes, ‘Yo, stop, stop, stop. Come here,’ ” Doo recalled. “And he grabs the bigs and he goes, ‘Hey, this is our job. You see that man? That man, Paul Pierce, is your scorer. Ray Allen is your scorer. You get them open. That’s all you do.

“If you get a rebound and put it back in, that’s great. But don’t look for the ball and don’t ask for the ball. You don’t see me ask for it and you don’t ask for it. Do your job, get rebounds, and that’s it. So who are our scorers?’ ”

From then on, the young frontcourt players knew exactly who their scorers were.


Garnett always looked out for his teammates, Doo said. During one road trip, the Celtics wanted special dinners for a flight home, then realized the meals would exceed the travel budget. So Garnett paid for the food, unbeknownst to the others.

When Garnett signed with the Chinese shoe company Anta, he asked Doo, a third-generation Chinese-American, to join him on a trip to the country. Doo had never been there before.

“This is part of my heritage, you know?” said Doo, his eyes beginning to well up. “He just said, ‘Hey, I want you to come. You helped train me, you’re part of my crew, and this is home for you.’”

During one off-day while the team was in New York in 2012, Garnett wanted to get to Boston to check on his pregnant wife, Brandi. He also knew that Doo had not seen his wife and children for a while. So he rented a private jet for the two of them.

“We’d talk about our baby girls all the time,” Doo said. “How do you raise them? What’s important in life?”

Doo sees players come and go. It is the nature of his job. But Garnett’s trade to Brooklyn in 2013 was difficult for him. Before Garnett left, Doo brought him a Roman gladiator mask to remind him of their memorable trip to Italy with the Celtics.

The two remain close, most recently texting about Garnett’s retirement. And Doo still wears the suit Garnett bought for him in 2008. He calls it the “KG Special.”

“When I wear my suit, I feel good,” Doo said. “KG would always say, ‘You know, B-Doo, you look good, you feel good. You feel good, you do well.’”

</comment><comment created_utc="1475425706.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8awl78" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8amkjv" controversiality="0">Thanks so much, Mr. Hero. </comment></comments></submission>
<submission author_name="mattycblazah" subreddit_name="bostonceltics" created_utc="1475322046.0" edited="False" has_media="False" gilded="0" score="10" title="Any footage of last night's scrimmage anywhere?" id="55cuyb" domain="self.bostonceltics" url="https://www.reddit.com/r/bostonceltics/comments/55cuyb/any_footage_of_last_nights_scrimmage_anywhere/" permalink="/r/bostonceltics/comments/55cuyb/any_footage_of_last_nights_scrimmage_anywhere/?ref=search_posts" locked="False" over_18="False" stickied="False" is_self="True" num_reports="" num_com_found="3" num_com_listed="3" handle="bostonceltics_2016.0-10.0">Title.<comments><comment created_utc="1475325843.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89hzff" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55cuyb" controversiality="0">just some highlights
http://www.csnne.com/celtics-scrimmage

the 2nd unit is legit</comment><comment created_utc="1475338914.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89oqof" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89hzff" controversiality="0">video didnt work for me</comment><comment created_utc="1475358512.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a1ctk" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89oqof" controversiality="0">http://www.csnne.com/video/highlights-celtics-scrimmage</comment></comments></submission>
<submission author_name="6FanForever" subreddit_name="bostonceltics" created_utc="1475307649.0" edited="False" has_media="False" gilded="0" score="6" title="Likely or Unlikely #2: Jordan Mickey becomes a rotation player?" id="55cavu" domain="self.bostonceltics" url="https://www.reddit.com/r/bostonceltics/comments/55cavu/likely_or_unlikely_2_jordan_mickey_becomes_a/" permalink="/r/bostonceltics/comments/55cavu/likely_or_unlikely_2_jordan_mickey_becomes_a/?ref=search_posts" locked="False" over_18="False" stickied="False" is_self="True" num_reports="" num_com_found="16" num_com_listed="16" handle="bostonceltics_2016.0-10.0">How it could happen:  KO’s delayed return allows Mickey to get minutes.  Mickey provides serious rim protection, solid rebounding and hard-nosed defense while shooting above 30% from three (shot 35% in the D-League last year).  Decent 3pt shooting along with rim protection superior to KO and Jerebko keeps him in the rotation.<comments><comment created_utc="1475310058.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89dpf5" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55cavu" controversiality="0">I'm gonna go with Unlikely on this one. The front court is just too crowded with better more experienced players. Horford, Amir, JerebGOAT, Zeller are all going to get some extended run in Kelly's absence. Specifically JerebGOAT. We will also run small ball lineups where Crowder and or Jaylen at the 4. Clogging it up even more. I would say it's definitely possible but highly unlikely just because he won't get the minutes. We might have to wait another year or two before we unleash GOAT Mickey. I am rooting for him to become a rotation player however! </comment><comment created_utc="1475354463.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89yr6n" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55cavu" controversiality="0">If he is something went really wrong or really right</comment><comment created_utc="1475324501.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89hiao" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55cavu" controversiality="0">Maybe next season when the front court should be thinned out a bit.</comment><comment created_utc="1475318676.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89fui0" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89dpf5" controversiality="0">&gt;  

The problem with waiting for next yr, assuming we keep KO and let Amir walk is Yabu and Zizic may be coming back from overseas and there's a chance we draft a 4 (Looking at you Giles). So there might be more guys for that 5th big man spot.</comment><comment created_utc="1475349594.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89vlgk" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89dpf5" controversiality="0">I'd play Mickey over Zeller, Zeller is never going to be anything especially good but Mickey has real potential.</comment><comment created_utc="1475331489.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89kfwt" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89fui0" controversiality="0">I don't think we will keep KO he's gonna be expensive</comment><comment created_utc="1475331581.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89khiq" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89fui0" controversiality="0">We're letting Amir walk? Why?! I like him!</comment><comment created_utc="1475340965.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89q2r2" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89fui0" controversiality="0">Why are we assuming that the C's will keep Kelly? He's likely going to demand $15-20 million next offseason and there are players down the pipeline who can fill-in admirably for him. There's Yabu and Zizic (and maybe even Giles, if the C's decide to take him). Jordan will need to compete with them, but since he possesses very good shot-blocking ability and an improving outside shot, he will have an advantage over them. </comment><comment created_utc="1475349842.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89vr4v" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89vlgk" controversiality="0">I agree, but Brad has shown us he likes more experienced players unless they have proven they deserve minutes. I don't think Zeller will even get that many minutes. He's the last big on the bench. He might get 5 minutes a night until Kelly returns. </comment><comment created_utc="1475336184.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89n1sm" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89kfwt" controversiality="0">But we could keep his Qualifying Offer on the books, renounce amir and JJ sign a max FA and then go over the cap for kelly's deal. *I think, not a cap-ologist.</comment><comment created_utc="1475390852.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aj06q" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89kfwt" controversiality="0">never know. sullinger went for under 7 million this summer when most people expected him to get at least 10 million.</comment><comment created_utc="1475343402.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89rnfi" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89n1sm" controversiality="0">maybe but it all depends on the market. I wouldn't resign him for ET money; even tho I love him we have enough big depth to be fine without him. </comment><comment created_utc="1475404668.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8amymt" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89n1sm" controversiality="0">that's what I initially thought, but Kelly's cap hold is higher than his QO. we can't do both.</comment><comment created_utc="1475412406.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8ap926" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89n1sm" controversiality="0">Not worth it if Jaylen Brown proves himself as a rookie and/or we are in a position to draft our big of the future.</comment><comment created_utc="1475427192.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8axn3r" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8amymt" controversiality="0">damn. does one work though?
</comment><comment created_utc="1475467774.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8bqfb3" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8axn3r" controversiality="0">Sorry, I meant we'd have to renounce Kelly to sign a max free agent.</comment></comments></submission>
<submission author_name="pobo90" subreddit_name="bostonceltics" created_utc="1475300868.0" edited="False" has_media="False" gilded="0" score="3" title="James Young" id="55c0s0" domain="self.bostonceltics" url="https://www.reddit.com/r/bostonceltics/comments/55c0s0/james_young/" permalink="/r/bostonceltics/comments/55c0s0/james_young/?ref=search_posts" locked="False" over_18="False" stickied="False" is_self="True" num_reports="" num_com_found="19" num_com_listed="19" handle="bostonceltics_2016.0-10.0">I have a strange feeling about this guy. He's gonna do things this year. <comments><comment created_utc="1475303703.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89bsu1" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55c0s0" controversiality="0">Well he's currently done zero things this far, so even one thing I'll take. </comment><comment created_utc="1475301980.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89b7bi" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55c0s0" controversiality="0">I don't know what makes you say that, but I hope so too!</comment><comment created_utc="1475304461.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89c1s8" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55c0s0" controversiality="0">How did he look in the scrimmage?</comment><comment created_utc="1475331224.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89kb9e" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55c0s0" controversiality="0">Things, like play for the Red Claws all year. </comment><comment created_utc="1475348809.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89v3lm" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55c0s0" controversiality="0">He has 2 positions he can play. 

SG - Bradley, Smart, Green, Rozier Hunter/Young

SF - Crowder, Brown, Green, Young

I just don't see how he's even going to get the minutes</comment><comment created_utc="1475364832.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a5beg" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55c0s0" controversiality="0">Yeah he'll be a big boost for a team in Turkey.</comment><comment created_utc="1475306532.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89cpqx" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55c0s0" controversiality="0">It's him or rj right? Young will have to show a lot to prove he's worth the risk over hunter's upside. Haven't heard much about either yet though</comment><comment created_utc="1475355373.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89zcw5" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55c0s0" controversiality="0">He will bring us the big fish in a trade, if that's what you mean</comment><comment created_utc="1475358516.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a1cwm" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55c0s0" controversiality="0">I mean, he said he's trying to model his game after Paul George, so that's great.

I still don't see him ever doing anything of consequence in the NBA.</comment><comment created_utc="1475339193.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89ox9y" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55c0s0" controversiality="0">Been feeling that way the last two years, I really hope the kid can finally make an impact this year </comment><comment created_utc="1475320117.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89g7i9" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89c1s8" controversiality="0">Real aggressive, had a nice assist to Amir on a fast break and actually helped spark a run for the team when he was subbed in.</comment><comment created_utc="1475352031.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89x5k4" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89c1s8" controversiality="0">Here's the real answer: He looked lost and still can't dribble.</comment><comment created_utc="1475327523.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89in1a" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89cpqx" controversiality="0">Depends on how you view the Jackson signing. There is a possible scenario where both RJ and Young are still on the team. </comment><comment created_utc="1475328283.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89iymd" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89cpqx" controversiality="0">Hunter's upside is almost nonexistent. </comment><comment created_utc="1475321968.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89gpl9" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89g7i9" controversiality="0">Now we're talking, didn't watch the game, but it's great to hear he's being more aggresive. I somewhy really want Young to succeed, with us..</comment><comment created_utc="1475357257.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a0ko4" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89x5k4" controversiality="0">He had one nice drive to the hoop. Drove at one of the bigs (Zeller maybe?), missed the layup but sprung up quickly to get the board and the lay-in. That was a promising series.


I was impressed with what he was doing, more so than RJ for sure. </comment><comment created_utc="1475332658.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89l1if" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89iymd" controversiality="0">He can be a solid rotational player. Has a good BBIQ. Is an above-average passer. All he needs to do is start draining some threes and he can carve out a serviceable NBA career. 

It's like everyone on this sub forgot the flashes of potential he displayed last season after a so-so performance in the Summer League. </comment><comment created_utc="1475338569.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89oitm" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89gpl9" controversiality="0">He's outplayed R.J. so far. It's not saying much because R.J. was a non factor but Young has looked somewhat competent.</comment><comment created_utc="1475358511.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a1cs4" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a0ko4" controversiality="0">That I agree with. RJ is a nobody out there unfortunately.</comment></comments></submission>
<submission author_name="hoodsiecup" subreddit_name="bostonceltics" created_utc="1475363569.0" edited="False" has_media="False" gilded="0" score="48" title="Kudos to the C's (Red Sox ceremony)" id="55fpvs" domain="self.bostonceltics" url="https://www.reddit.com/r/bostonceltics/comments/55fpvs/kudos_to_the_cs_red_sox_ceremony/" permalink="/r/bostonceltics/comments/55fpvs/kudos_to_the_cs_red_sox_ceremony/?ref=search_posts" locked="False" over_18="False" stickied="False" is_self="True" num_reports="" num_com_found="13" num_com_listed="13" handle="bostonceltics_2016.0-10.0">Coach Stevens and the entire Celtics roster was at Fenway tonight before the game celebrating David Ortiz and his last Fenway series in the regular season.

Each player was wearing a home jersey with Ortiz's name and number in the back. They all took selfies and got their jerseys signed by Big Papi too, which I though was pretty cool.

Overall it was a classy move on their part to show up in full force on a Saturday night and support the city the way they did. Kudos to those guys, definitely a good group of people.<comments><comment created_utc="1475364215.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a4yf3" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fpvs" controversiality="0">[C's honoring Pierce... err, I mean Big Papi!] (https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Ctt6uqwWIAAeTgC.jpg)</comment><comment created_utc="1475364005.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a4tu4" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fpvs" controversiality="0">BOSTON SPORTS &lt;3</comment><comment created_utc="1475364699.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a58mt" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fpvs" controversiality="0">Here's a vid of them congratulating David Ortiz for a stellar career: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eiwRjK-nsEo</comment><comment created_utc="1475385127.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8agr1r" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fpvs" controversiality="0">Now that I have lived in cities other than Boston I really do appreciate the brotherhood among the different teams.  It's cool, man.</comment><comment created_utc="1475446237.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8bcej5" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fpvs" controversiality="0">I saw 34 and I literally jumped out of my seat, then I realized everyone had 34 and I realized </comment><comment created_utc="1475378121.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8ad36d" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fpvs" controversiality="0">The worst part about Florida State's loss is that North Carolina's final drive and game winning field goal came during this time so I didn't get to enjoy it because I was watching my shitty Noles lose a heartbreaker. </comment><comment created_utc="1475439823.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8b7m4a" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a4yf3" controversiality="0">Thanks for sharing, so adorable! </comment><comment created_utc="1475373048.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aa5fw" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a4tu4" controversiality="0">34 is just a good number for you folks, isn't it?</comment><comment created_utc="1475378349.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8ad7us" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8ad36d" controversiality="0">Uhhh wrong thread man?</comment><comment created_utc="1475379053.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8adlpk" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8aa5fw" controversiality="0">Why yes. Yes it is.</comment><comment created_utc="1475594696.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8dmf0p" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8aa5fw" controversiality="0">So is 33 ;)</comment><comment created_utc="1475414874.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aq8x0" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8ad7us" controversiality="1">I mean, it was unnecessary for me to bring up, but I was in the right thread. I'm still seething over that loss and the fact that it happened right during the Celtics coming out on Fenway made it worse. I would have liked to see the Red Sox ceremony, but I was too busy watching a shitty ending to a football game. </comment><comment created_utc="1475432913.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8b23f6" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8aq8x0" controversiality="0">My bad man. Sorry about the loss.</comment></comments></submission>
<submission author_name="pokersquirrel" subreddit_name="bostonceltics" created_utc="1475361114.0" edited="False" has_media="False" gilded="0" score="9" title="Parallels between Chauncy/Rip/Sheed Pistons &amp; Current C's." id="55fjvu" domain="self.bostonceltics" url="https://www.reddit.com/r/bostonceltics/comments/55fjvu/parallels_between_chauncyripsheed_pistons_current/" permalink="/r/bostonceltics/comments/55fjvu/parallels_between_chauncyripsheed_pistons_current/?ref=search_posts" locked="False" over_18="False" stickied="False" is_self="True" num_reports="" num_com_found="10" num_com_listed="10" handle="bostonceltics_2016.0-10.0">Hungry, under-appreciated, blue collar work ethic, high motors, defensive pride, team spirit. 2007-2008 C's rivalry with those Pistons was fun, but it was clear they were in their twilight. 

These C's, however...<comments><comment created_utc="1475368549.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a7ihq" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">That Pistons squad is by far one of my favorite non-Celtics teams. So much fun to watch, and that frontcourt was dirty!</comment><comment created_utc="1475368922.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a7q8o" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">I wish we could have that type of season however due to the change in the hand checking rule it is pretty much impossible to have a defense as effective as that champion Pistons squad. However I definitely see 14-15 Hawks potential out of this team.</comment><comment created_utc="1475381177.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aerk1" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">Moreso with the Big3 era Celtics. Both had a hard-nosed defensive identity. 

Both won a championship, and had one other Finals appearance (lost in 7 to Duncan's Spurs and Kobe's Lakers, respectively).

Both sent 4 of 5 starters to the all-star game, something that rarely happens.

Also, Chauncey and KG are best bros</comment><comment created_utc="1475362155.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a3n5w" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">I love tough basketball players and this team is filled with them. Can't wait to finally see them in full action. </comment><comment created_utc="1475384746.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8agk56" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">The similarity is that both teams didnt have a real star but collectively were better than their individual talents.

I kind of hate sports hyperbole. WTF does blue collar work ethic mean? I would argue that the Celtics/Pistons (or any good defensive team) play very High IQ basketball with maximum effort. That sounds more like a Wall Street banker/lawyer working at a big firm than a Plumber.  </comment><comment created_utc="1475380676.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aehlg" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">It goes further than that:

* Billups/IT: score-first guard with underrated passing skills
* Rip/AB: king of the mid-range off screens
* Prince/Crowder: tenacious defender and slasher
* Sheed/Horford: do-it-all big man with 3pt range
* Ben/Amir: I'm here for defence &amp; rebounds</comment><comment created_utc="1475363665.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a4lnh" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">Chauncey-Rip-Prince-Sheed-Big Ben vs. IT-AB-Jae-Amir-Horford? If I squint hard enough, I could see it. We need an MVP-type season from IT and/or Horford. Capture the LOB trophy in June and I'll be completely sold.</comment><comment created_utc="1475462318.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8bn3b2" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a7ihq" controversiality="0">Sheed was so much like KG in that you loved to hate him, but deep down you'd love having him on your team. Wish he had more in the tank by the time he joined the green.</comment><comment created_utc="1475384435.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8agejm" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a4lnh" controversiality="0">I think the defensive ability of Ben Wallace vs Amir Johnson is a huuuge difference there</comment><comment created_utc="1475390751.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aiyzj" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8agejm" controversiality="0">theres a big difference in talent in most of the positions lol</comment></comments></submission>
</subcorpus>
