<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<reddit>
  <submission author_name="6FanForever" subreddit_name="bostonceltics" created_utc="1475307649.0" edited="False" has_media="False" gilded="0" score="6" title="Likely or Unlikely #2: Jordan Mickey becomes a rotation player?" id="55cavu" domain="self.bostonceltics" url="https://www.reddit.com/r/bostonceltics/comments/55cavu/likely_or_unlikely_2_jordan_mickey_becomes_a/" permalink="/r/bostonceltics/comments/55cavu/likely_or_unlikely_2_jordan_mickey_becomes_a/?ref=search_posts" locked="False" over_18="False" stickied="False" is_self="True" num_reports="" num_com_found="16" num_com_listed="16">How it could happen:  KO’s delayed return allows Mickey to get minutes.  Mickey provides serious rim protection, solid rebounding and hard-nosed defense while shooting above 30% from three (shot 35% in the D-League last year).  Decent 3pt shooting along with rim protection superior to KO and Jerebko keeps him in the rotation.<comments><comment created_utc="1475310058.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89dpf5" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55cavu" controversiality="0">I'm gonna go with Unlikely on this one. The front court is just too crowded with better more experienced players. Horford, Amir, JerebGOAT, Zeller are all going to get some extended run in Kelly's absence. Specifically JerebGOAT. We will also run small ball lineups where Crowder and or Jaylen at the 4. Clogging it up even more. I would say it's definitely possible but highly unlikely just because he won't get the minutes. We might have to wait another year or two before we unleash GOAT Mickey. I am rooting for him to become a rotation player however! </comment><comment created_utc="1475354463.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89yr6n" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55cavu" controversiality="0">If he is something went really wrong or really right</comment><comment created_utc="1475324501.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89hiao" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55cavu" controversiality="0">Maybe next season when the front court should be thinned out a bit.</comment><comment created_utc="1475318676.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89fui0" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89dpf5" controversiality="0">&gt;  

The problem with waiting for next yr, assuming we keep KO and let Amir walk is Yabu and Zizic may be coming back from overseas and there's a chance we draft a 4 (Looking at you Giles). So there might be more guys for that 5th big man spot.</comment><comment created_utc="1475349594.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89vlgk" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89dpf5" controversiality="0">I'd play Mickey over Zeller, Zeller is never going to be anything especially good but Mickey has real potential.</comment><comment created_utc="1475331489.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89kfwt" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89fui0" controversiality="0">I don't think we will keep KO he's gonna be expensive</comment><comment created_utc="1475331581.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89khiq" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89fui0" controversiality="0">We're letting Amir walk? Why?! I like him!</comment><comment created_utc="1475340965.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89q2r2" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89fui0" controversiality="0">Why are we assuming that the C's will keep Kelly? He's likely going to demand $15-20 million next offseason and there are players down the pipeline who can fill-in admirably for him. There's Yabu and Zizic (and maybe even Giles, if the C's decide to take him). Jordan will need to compete with them, but since he possesses very good shot-blocking ability and an improving outside shot, he will have an advantage over them. </comment><comment created_utc="1475349842.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89vr4v" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89vlgk" controversiality="0">I agree, but Brad has shown us he likes more experienced players unless they have proven they deserve minutes. I don't think Zeller will even get that many minutes. He's the last big on the bench. He might get 5 minutes a night until Kelly returns. </comment><comment created_utc="1475336184.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89n1sm" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89kfwt" controversiality="0">But we could keep his Qualifying Offer on the books, renounce amir and JJ sign a max FA and then go over the cap for kelly's deal. *I think, not a cap-ologist.</comment><comment created_utc="1475390852.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aj06q" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89kfwt" controversiality="0">never know. sullinger went for under 7 million this summer when most people expected him to get at least 10 million.</comment><comment created_utc="1475343402.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89rnfi" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89n1sm" controversiality="0">maybe but it all depends on the market. I wouldn't resign him for ET money; even tho I love him we have enough big depth to be fine without him. </comment><comment created_utc="1475404668.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8amymt" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89n1sm" controversiality="0">that's what I initially thought, but Kelly's cap hold is higher than his QO. we can't do both.</comment><comment created_utc="1475412406.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8ap926" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89n1sm" controversiality="0">Not worth it if Jaylen Brown proves himself as a rookie and/or we are in a position to draft our big of the future.</comment><comment created_utc="1475427192.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8axn3r" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8amymt" controversiality="0">damn. does one work though?
</comment><comment created_utc="1475467774.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8bqfb3" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8axn3r" controversiality="0">Sorry, I meant we'd have to renounce Kelly to sign a max free agent.</comment></comments></submission>
</reddit>
