<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<reddit>
  <submission author_name="celticsbig4" subreddit_name="bostonceltics" created_utc="1475346550.0" edited="False" has_media="False" gilded="0" score="67" title="A look at Smart's new shooting form" id="55eh6b" domain="self.bostonceltics" url="https://www.reddit.com/r/bostonceltics/comments/55eh6b/a_look_at_smarts_new_shooting_form/" permalink="/r/bostonceltics/comments/55eh6b/a_look_at_smarts_new_shooting_form/?ref=search_posts" locked="False" over_18="False" stickied="False" is_self="True" num_reports="" num_com_found="22" num_com_listed="22">https://youtu.be/LJXLqkp3-pw

There's still a dip but it's quick, almost unnoticeable compared to the huge dip in his shot last year. Feet are set more consistently as well, which was probably the biggest problem with his shot even in college. It looks like he's getting set quicker and and having a consistent overall motion, but it's only training camp so we'll see what happens once real games start.<comments><comment created_utc="1475347199.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89u2f2" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">He had at least two really clean catch-and-shoot threes go in during the scrimmage. He didn't have to chuck a bunch of wild ones to get in a groove, either. </comment><comment created_utc="1475349574.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89vl0r" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">Not only does this new form save time on the shot but I'm sure it saves him some energy too. That old form had way too much built into it. </comment><comment created_utc="1475366947.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a6kik" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">Its because his hair is shorter and no longer in the way (please get this reference...)</comment><comment created_utc="1475350251.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89w0qw" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">Here's Jared's video for even better quality: https://twitter.com/JaredWeissNBA/status/782247192602021888</comment><comment created_utc="1475352756.0" edited="1475353127.0" gilded="0" id="d89xmgr" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">Looks a lot smoother and simpler. In previous seasons, there appeared to be too much motion before going into the shot.</comment><comment created_utc="1475380201.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8ae8c4" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">It appears to go in. I like it.</comment><comment created_utc="1475351953.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89x3qs" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">WTF? - Am I watching a video of Devin Booker??? That's crazy. Great find OP. With that video and his performance yesterday - he could be a legit 3 and D guy. And what's awesome is he also looked really good coming screens at the 2. I always thought of him as a PG but now I am not sure? </comment><comment created_utc="1475348981.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89v7jj" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">It looks like he's working on exactly what he needs to be working on. Good for him; I can't wait to see it in action</comment><comment created_utc="1475385289.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8agu0m" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">I will believe it when I see it.  Not to be a negative nancy, Smarts one of my binkys, but we hear these kinds of things all the time.  If he can get to 37%+ from three he's going to be a hell of a player.  </comment><comment created_utc="1475368797.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a7nq2" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">He doesn't seem to have much elevation on this shot at all... Which is fine if he is being encouraged to shoot only open jumpers... but inevitably; if you handle the ball you will need to shoot contested shots, which will mean changing your shot significantly and resulting in his contested shots % going down (if that is even possible). </comment><comment created_utc="1475373353.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aabk7" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">holy shit that is so much smoother than before. The horrible dip is gone and mechanics are much more efficient. HYPE HYPE HYPE HYPE</comment><comment created_utc="1475389099.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aiegw" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">He doesn't hurl the ball at the hoop anymore. It's more consistent and it's quicker. I love it</comment><comment created_utc="1475506567.0" edited="1475513563.0" gilded="0" id="d8c5uvp" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55eh6b" controversiality="0">As we have been saying for two years. If he can improve his offense to just bad instead of historically bad, he will be MUCH more valuable than he already was. If his offense gets to above average he will be a star. </comment><comment created_utc="1475354080.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d89yhso" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89vl0r" controversiality="0">The old form looked like he was in pain while shooting it. It seemed so laborious and difficult. This one looks nice and smooth. I hope it results in better percentages for him, although his biggest issue is still shot selection. </comment><comment created_utc="1475470095.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8brly8" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a6kik" controversiality="0">:) </comment><comment created_utc="1475363341.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a4ee2" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89w0qw" controversiality="0">Dip is so much nicer now. Kinda looks like pierces shot to me.</comment><comment created_utc="1475380707.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aei8j" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89xmgr" controversiality="0">Yea, he would bring the ball almost all the way to the top back part of his head.  It was ridiculous.  He like, catapulted it.  This looks a lot different and a lot better.  The less movement in the shooting form, the easier it is to replicate.  </comment><comment created_utc="1475434044.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8b2xzo" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89xmgr" controversiality="0">His shot had 2 unnecessary chamber motions. One was the dip at his knees and the other was at his head. </comment><comment created_utc="1475356717.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a08kz" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d89x3qs" controversiality="0">3 and D? cmon man he can be so much more.</comment><comment created_utc="1475388275.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8ai3fn" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a7nq2" controversiality="0">Don't know why you're being downvoted since it's a valid point. A shooting style with a low hop helps with consistency and maintain accuracy when you're tired, but it can be blocked easier. This is why Curry's main go-to moves are screens, and mastered dribbling/footwork to create separation during 1v1. A lot of guards shoot with a high hop and two-stroke motion ala Kobe/Jordan style because they aren't usually the tallest and need to make contested shots in traffic. You can have more than one shooting form, but not everyone can perfect all of them or use the right one by instinct every time. Pierce have multiple shooting forms but it took him years to develop and he adapted his game as he aged. </comment><comment created_utc="1475430687.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8b0bmf" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a4ee2" controversiality="0">I see it a little bit too man, good catch. </comment><comment created_utc="1475360166.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a2ev3" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a08kz" controversiality="0">You got me man. What was I thinking? 😉</comment></comments></submission>
</reddit>
