<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<reddit>
  <submission author_name="pokersquirrel" subreddit_name="bostonceltics" created_utc="1475361114.0" edited="False" has_media="False" gilded="0" score="9" title="Parallels between Chauncy/Rip/Sheed Pistons &amp; Current C's." id="55fjvu" domain="self.bostonceltics" url="https://www.reddit.com/r/bostonceltics/comments/55fjvu/parallels_between_chauncyripsheed_pistons_current/" permalink="/r/bostonceltics/comments/55fjvu/parallels_between_chauncyripsheed_pistons_current/?ref=search_posts" locked="False" over_18="False" stickied="False" is_self="True" num_reports="" num_com_found="10" num_com_listed="10">Hungry, under-appreciated, blue collar work ethic, high motors, defensive pride, team spirit. 2007-2008 C's rivalry with those Pistons was fun, but it was clear they were in their twilight. 

These C's, however...<comments><comment created_utc="1475368549.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a7ihq" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">That Pistons squad is by far one of my favorite non-Celtics teams. So much fun to watch, and that frontcourt was dirty!</comment><comment created_utc="1475368922.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a7q8o" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">I wish we could have that type of season however due to the change in the hand checking rule it is pretty much impossible to have a defense as effective as that champion Pistons squad. However I definitely see 14-15 Hawks potential out of this team.</comment><comment created_utc="1475381177.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aerk1" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">Moreso with the Big3 era Celtics. Both had a hard-nosed defensive identity. 

Both won a championship, and had one other Finals appearance (lost in 7 to Duncan's Spurs and Kobe's Lakers, respectively).

Both sent 4 of 5 starters to the all-star game, something that rarely happens.

Also, Chauncey and KG are best bros</comment><comment created_utc="1475362155.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a3n5w" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">I love tough basketball players and this team is filled with them. Can't wait to finally see them in full action. </comment><comment created_utc="1475384746.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8agk56" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">The similarity is that both teams didnt have a real star but collectively were better than their individual talents.

I kind of hate sports hyperbole. WTF does blue collar work ethic mean? I would argue that the Celtics/Pistons (or any good defensive team) play very High IQ basketball with maximum effort. That sounds more like a Wall Street banker/lawyer working at a big firm than a Plumber.  </comment><comment created_utc="1475380676.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aehlg" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">It goes further than that:

* Billups/IT: score-first guard with underrated passing skills
* Rip/AB: king of the mid-range off screens
* Prince/Crowder: tenacious defender and slasher
* Sheed/Horford: do-it-all big man with 3pt range
* Ben/Amir: I'm here for defence &amp; rebounds</comment><comment created_utc="1475363665.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8a4lnh" num_reports="" parent_id="t3_55fjvu" controversiality="0">Chauncey-Rip-Prince-Sheed-Big Ben vs. IT-AB-Jae-Amir-Horford? If I squint hard enough, I could see it. We need an MVP-type season from IT and/or Horford. Capture the LOB trophy in June and I'll be completely sold.</comment><comment created_utc="1475462318.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8bn3b2" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a7ihq" controversiality="0">Sheed was so much like KG in that you loved to hate him, but deep down you'd love having him on your team. Wish he had more in the tank by the time he joined the green.</comment><comment created_utc="1475384435.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8agejm" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8a4lnh" controversiality="0">I think the defensive ability of Ben Wallace vs Amir Johnson is a huuuge difference there</comment><comment created_utc="1475390751.0" edited="False" gilded="0" id="d8aiyzj" num_reports="" parent_id="t1_d8agejm" controversiality="0">theres a big difference in talent in most of the positions lol</comment></comments></submission>
</reddit>
